

# DELVIN ROPHT CHEMISTRY TEACHER

## **Summary**

Experienced Chemistry Tutor provides individual and small group sessions for high school and undergraduate students. Acting as mentor and coach, integrates effective learning and study strategies to enhance academic progress. Guides students through creative processes that help them become better students and independent critical thinkers with skills that go beyond any specific course or subject.

## **Work Experience**

**Chemistry Tutor** 

Chemistry Tutor – March 2012 to Present A-One, Sydney, Australia

- Meet with student's 10th to 12th grade looking to improve their comprehension of Chemistry.
- Use Board of Education approved curriculum and materials to gauge and coach students to achieve academic goals.

- Perform small and safe chemical experiments to enhance learning experience with small groups.
- Work with students on homework assignments, coaching them in strategies for finding their own solutions.
- Helped students realize how basic Chemistry governs all other sciences.

#### **Chemistry Tutor**

#### **Chemistry Tutor – March 2014 to Present** Winston Academy, Los Angeles, USA

- Work with undergraduate students on essays, test papers and post-graduate programs
- Review assignments and conduct examinations to offer appropriate feedback.
- Meet with Dean of Science to discuss ways to improve curriculum.
- Developed action plans based on students and educators academic goals
- Work effectively with students with diverse learning needs and cultural backgrounds

#### **Education**

#### **Single Subject Teaching Credential: Chemistry**

- Bachelors Of Science in Chemistry May 2016(Bethany College Bethany, WV)
- Passed American Association of Chemistry Teachers (AACT) in 2018

### Contact

Address: 123 Fake Street | City, State, Zip Code

• **Date of birth:** 1999-19-09 • Nationality: Australia

• **Phone number:** (555)-555-5555 99 • Email address: info@qwikresume.com • Website: www.qwikresume.com

• LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume

## **Skills**

- Teaching Skills
- Communication Skills
- Monitoring Skills

## **Core Competencies**

- Parent-teacher relations
- Multimedia learning technologies
- Educational services administration
- Online learning
- Interactive teaching/learning

## **Hobbies**

- Reading
- Planning
- Writing
- Editing
- Enjoying drink